Matt: I find there's a, a slight
disjunct between sort of people
that I meet or encounter in work and
what I see in mainstream media and
what I see online, because of course
online, you filter to things much
more towards your own interests.
So there's much more
exposure to that information.
And on the whole it's much more,
much more accurate online, at
least in the places that I go.
In the mainstream media, there seems
to be very little understanding
of of autism beyond the kind of
vague impression of what it is.
It also seems ... for obvious
reasons to focus mainly on children.
And there seems to be less awareness of
how it affects adults and particularly
women and girls, that seems to be a
much less explored the area that's only
kind of currently coming into ... coming
into, into people's perception.
In terms of fiction it's
often pretty infuriating.
It's still, it's still either people who
are hopeless or who are robotic or where
it, there's some kind of autistics advance
and it's, it's like a, like a super power.
Which doesn't really reflect the
diversity of autistic people in any way.